CINDY PHAM

VISUAL DESIGNER



PROFILE

Cindy Pham is a designer who specializes in design strategy, brand development, and user interface and experience. The roots of her passion stem from her fascination with storytelling through visual arts and interactive digital experiences. Her work has garnered awards and earned her a spot on the jury panel for the FWA.

RECOGNITION

2017 ADC Merit Award

2017 ADDY Award

2017 Webby Awards Honoree

2016 Design Student Spotlight

Awwwards - Site of the Day

FWA - Site of the Day

Press: AdWeek

Press: Fast Company

Press: Mashable

CLIENTS

Google, YouTube, Adult Swim, Spotify,
Oxygen TV, Pinterest, ŌURA Ring,

Downtown Norfolk Council, UC Davis

EXPERIENCE

October 2017 - Present

The FWA | Judge

Served on a jury panel for the FWA, which showcases the most progressive and forward-thinking projects created by individuals, agencies, and brands.

June 2016 - Present

Grow | Creative

Worked in an award-winning digital agency to design intelligent and engaging interactive experiences for a wide range of client types and target platforms, including Google, YouTube, Spotify, and Adult Swim.

November 2015 - June 2016

UCD Design Career Fair | Graphics Team Lead

Directed 10+ designers to create a cohesive brand identity and creative direction for a design career fair with an audience of 100+ students and 20+ employers.

EDUCATION

2012 - 2016

Design, B.A.

University of California, Davis

CONTACT

Website | cindypham.com

Email | cindycancreate@gmail.com

Phone | 408 406 7449